Chandra Mishra

Image Processing Expert - RajCOMP Survey in Department of Information Technology & Communication

Jaipur, Rajasthan chandramis3_nxa@indeedemail.com +91 9015425689

I have more 2.0 years working experience in the field of GIS, Remote Sensing good exposure and practically in satellite data in 2D and software particularly used Arc GIS, ERDAS Imaging, QGIS work in an exciting and professional environment of an organization and achieve excellence through dedicated efforts, I am committed towards developing my career and skills gained from experience and study of GIS into practice as a professional GIS Engineer in a dynamic, fast paced GIS business consulting environment.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Image Processing Expert

RajCOMP Survey in Department of Information Technology & Communication - Jaipur, Rajasthan January 2018 to Present

Jaipur, deputed by Quantum Asia Pvt Ltd, Since 05, January, 2018 to till date.

- Working As a Image Processing Expert On Project MJSA Project (Mukhya mantri Jal Swavalmban Abhiyan) Bharatpur Watershed Department (Government Of Rajasthan) Since March 27.2017 to Dec 2018.
- Working As a Gis Excutive on Project Government of Rajasthan For RAJCOME Project Jaipur Since July 2016 to March 2017
- Nature of Duties:- Production of Land base mapping Like Road Centerline Building, Using Satellite Image, Geo reference of Village Khasra Map with the help of Google Earth and Online Satellite Imaging with ArcGis, POI Data integration of Rajasthan area,

BANARAS HINDU UNIVERCITY - Mirzapur, Uttar Pradesh March 2016 to June 2016

Role: - Dissertation

Project Name: - Remote Sensing & GIS in Dairy Farming and Land use & Land Cover RGSC

Barkachha & Surrounding area, Mirzapur, U.P.

Description: - Mapping of, Land Use & Land Cover mapping.

Responsibility:

- Land base uploaded
- Land Use & Land Cover Planning.
- Ground Water Potential Zone.
- Operations are carried out in Arc GIS-9.3.

CORE STRENGTHS:-

- ➤ Optimistic, Self-confidence.
- > Ability to think out of the box, want to make a difference.
- > Ability to work individually as well as with team.
- ➤ Desire to learn.
- > Self motivated.
- > Can adjust in different conditions.

PERSONAL PROFILE:-

Father's Name: Mr. Tej Narayan Mishra

Education

PG Diploma in Remote Sensing and GIS

Banaras Hindu University - Varanasi, Uttar Pradesh

Geography

Kurukhetra University

B.A in Geography

Delhi University - Delhi, Delhi

CBSE

Bihar Board - Delhi, Delhi

Skills / IT Skills

• arc gis erdas imagine